<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>amendment on Belmont-MA.info</title>
    <link>/tags/amendment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in amendment on Belmont-MA.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/amendment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Withdrawing my amendment to Article 10</title>
      <link>/withdrawing-article-10-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/withdrawing-article-10-amendment/</guid>
      <description>I first state my reasons for why I believe it makes sense to replace Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day. I then provide a number of different thoughts related to withdrawing my amendment.
The case for replacing Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day First, I don&amp;rsquo;t believe Columbus is deserving of a holiday or great respect. Like so many historic figures, his legacy is a mixed one, but it&amp;rsquo;s a mixed legacy that strikes me as far more negative than positive, as others have well articulated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My amendment for article 10</title>
      <link>/article-10-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/article-10-amendment/</guid>
      <description>Summary of this post and my position on article 10 I support Article 10, the resolution to replace Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day in Belmont, and I proposed an amendment to standardize the punctuation of the name of the day, to reduce the chance of misreading a particular sentence, and to address concerns about the inaccuracy of some historical claims.
I intend to vote in favor of Article 10 regardless of whether my amendment passes, though I believe my amendment includes some improvements and helps promote an important norm of intellectual honesty.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
