<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>website on Belmont-MA.info</title>
    <link>/categories/website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in website on Belmont-MA.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eliminate unnecessary credentials in hiring</title>
      <link>/eliminate-unnecessary-credentials-in-hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/eliminate-unnecessary-credentials-in-hiring/</guid>
      <description>Making Belmont hiring more inclusive by eliminating unnecessary credential requirements Recent stories in the Wall Street Journal and New York Times discuss how companies are eliminating unnecessary degree requirements for jobs and are moving to testing directly whether applicants can do the jobs advertised. Maryland is doing the same by eliminating unnecessary degree requirements for many state level jobs.
By eliminating unnecessary credential requirements, Belmont and Belmont Public Schools can make their hiring processes more inclusive, in particular to those who come from lower socio-economic backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appointment to the solid waste and recycling committee</title>
      <link>/appointment-to-solid-waste-and-recycling-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/appointment-to-solid-waste-and-recycling-committee/</guid>
      <description>Update I was appointed to the Solid Waste and Recycling Committee. The committee charge is to &amp;ldquo;assist the Town in procuring a new collection contract and to consider possible enhancements in recycling efforts.&amp;rdquo;
If you have any views on this, please get in touch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review hiring practices to help achieve diversity, equity, and inclusion goals</title>
      <link>/review-hiring-practices-to-help-achieve-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/review-hiring-practices-to-help-achieve-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-goals/</guid>
      <description>Context I&amp;rsquo;ve sent the letter below to a few of the different town publications in the hope that it will get published.
Update (2021.11.23): The commentary ran in the Belmont Citizen-Herald.
Review hiring practices to help achieve diversity, equity, and inclusion goals This past summer, I had the privilege of serving on the screening committee for Belmont Public Schools’ Director of Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion. The experience caused me to reflect on how important hiring practices are to achieving DEI-related goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking out loud about overnight parking</title>
      <link>/thinking-out-loud-about-overnight-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinking-out-loud-about-overnight-parking/</guid>
      <description>Context At the October 13 Diversity Task Force meeting, the idea of removing the overnight parking ban was floated as a way to address a racial and economic equity issue in town. I thought about the issue for several days, and collected my thoughts into an email which I sent to a few of the attendees on October 22. I&amp;rsquo;m sharing the body of that email so you can get a sense of my thinking on this issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking out loud about the BPS equity audit</title>
      <link>/thinking-out-loud-about-the-bps-equity-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinking-out-loud-about-the-bps-equity-audit/</guid>
      <description>Context I&amp;rsquo;ve attended most of the school committee&amp;rsquo;s equity subcommittee meetings since February. On October 22, I sent an email to the equity subcommittee with some concerns that what had been described early in the process was not obviously what we were seeing in the implementation. I also wanted to share some goal thoughts for discussion, because that had been a topic at the October 19 meeting and few concrete goal ideas had been shared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future plans for this site</title>
      <link>/future-plans-for-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/future-plans-for-this-site/</guid>
      <description>The plans  Whether I&amp;rsquo;m elected or not, I plan to release on this site an application that makes it easier to compare the voting records of our town meeting members. This is in the works. The town makes data available publicly, but the data is not consistent and there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of clean up to do before one can work with it. I also plan to share write-ups of information I&amp;rsquo;ve collected and my associated thoughts on issues related to the town (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
