<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>inclusivity on Belmont-MA.info</title>
    <link>/tags/inclusivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in inclusivity on Belmont-MA.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/inclusivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eliminate unnecessary credentials in hiring</title>
      <link>/eliminate-unnecessary-credentials-in-hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/eliminate-unnecessary-credentials-in-hiring/</guid>
      <description>Making Belmont hiring more inclusive by eliminating unnecessary credential requirements Recent stories in the Wall Street Journal and New York Times discuss how companies are eliminating unnecessary degree requirements for jobs and are moving to testing directly whether applicants can do the jobs advertised. Maryland is doing the same by eliminating unnecessary degree requirements for many state level jobs.
By eliminating unnecessary credential requirements, Belmont and Belmont Public Schools can make their hiring processes more inclusive, in particular to those who come from lower socio-economic backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review hiring practices to help achieve diversity, equity, and inclusion goals</title>
      <link>/review-hiring-practices-to-help-achieve-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/review-hiring-practices-to-help-achieve-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-goals/</guid>
      <description>Context I&amp;rsquo;ve sent the letter below to a few of the different town publications in the hope that it will get published.
Update (2021.11.23): The commentary ran in the Belmont Citizen-Herald.
Review hiring practices to help achieve diversity, equity, and inclusion goals This past summer, I had the privilege of serving on the screening committee for Belmont Public Schools’ Director of Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion. The experience caused me to reflect on how important hiring practices are to achieving DEI-related goals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
