<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>town meeting on Belmont-MA.info</title>
    <link>/tags/town-meeting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in town meeting on Belmont-MA.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/town-meeting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My opposition to the demolition delay bylaw amendment</title>
      <link>/my-opposition-to-the-demolition-delay-bylaw-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/my-opposition-to-the-demolition-delay-bylaw-amendment/</guid>
      <description>Explanation of opposition The demolition delay bylaw amendment (Article 4) that came before Town Meeting last night makes permanent what was a temporary demolition delay bylaw. The bylaw imposes a 12 month delay on developers who want to demolish buildings that are on the historic register. The amendment passed with a strong majority.
I wanted Town Meeting to oppose the amendment so the bylaw would expire, and I did a bad job of explaining reasons I believe we should have opposed it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Withdrawing my amendment to Article 10</title>
      <link>/withdrawing-article-10-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/withdrawing-article-10-amendment/</guid>
      <description>I first state my reasons for why I believe it makes sense to replace Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day. I then provide a number of different thoughts related to withdrawing my amendment.
The case for replacing Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day First, I don&amp;rsquo;t believe Columbus is deserving of a holiday or great respect. Like so many historic figures, his legacy is a mixed one, but it&amp;rsquo;s a mixed legacy that strikes me as far more negative than positive, as others have well articulated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My amendment for article 10</title>
      <link>/article-10-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/article-10-amendment/</guid>
      <description>Summary of this post and my position on article 10 I support Article 10, the resolution to replace Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day in Belmont, and I proposed an amendment to standardize the punctuation of the name of the day, to reduce the chance of misreading a particular sentence, and to address concerns about the inaccuracy of some historical claims.
I intend to vote in favor of Article 10 regardless of whether my amendment passes, though I believe my amendment includes some improvements and helps promote an important norm of intellectual honesty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me and why I&#39;m running</title>
      <link>/about-me-and-why-im-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-me-and-why-im-running/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m running for Town Meeting to represent Precinct 3 About me I’ve lived in Belmont for two years with my wife and now with our young daughter. I’m COO at MaxMind, a tech company headquartered in Waltham. My family and I very much enjoy the town, its parks, stores, the library, access to public transit, and the people we’ve met.
Why I&amp;rsquo;m seeking nomination I want to hold the town accountable for how it spends our tax money, and I want to ensure the services we receive in return run well and make sense.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
