<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Belmont-MA.info</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Belmont-MA.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Eliminate unnecessary credentials in hiring</title>
      <link>/eliminate-unnecessary-credentials-in-hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/eliminate-unnecessary-credentials-in-hiring/</guid>
      <description>Making Belmont hiring more inclusive by eliminating unnecessary credential requirements Recent stories in the Wall Street Journal and New York Times discuss how companies are eliminating unnecessary degree requirements for jobs and are moving to testing directly whether applicants can do the jobs advertised. Maryland is doing the same by eliminating unnecessary degree requirements for many state level jobs.
By eliminating unnecessary credential requirements, Belmont and Belmont Public Schools can make their hiring processes more inclusive, in particular to those who come from lower socio-economic backgrounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appointment to the solid waste and recycling committee</title>
      <link>/appointment-to-solid-waste-and-recycling-committee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/appointment-to-solid-waste-and-recycling-committee/</guid>
      <description>Update I was appointed to the Solid Waste and Recycling Committee. The committee charge is to &amp;ldquo;assist the Town in procuring a new collection contract and to consider possible enhancements in recycling efforts.&amp;rdquo;
If you have any views on this, please get in touch!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review hiring practices to help achieve diversity, equity, and inclusion goals</title>
      <link>/review-hiring-practices-to-help-achieve-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/review-hiring-practices-to-help-achieve-diversity-equity-and-inclusion-goals/</guid>
      <description>Context I&amp;rsquo;ve sent the letter below to a few of the different town publications in the hope that it will get published.
Update (2021.11.23): The commentary ran in the Belmont Citizen-Herald.
Review hiring practices to help achieve diversity, equity, and inclusion goals This past summer, I had the privilege of serving on the screening committee for Belmont Public Schools’ Director of Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion. The experience caused me to reflect on how important hiring practices are to achieving DEI-related goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking out loud about overnight parking</title>
      <link>/thinking-out-loud-about-overnight-parking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinking-out-loud-about-overnight-parking/</guid>
      <description>Context At the October 13 Diversity Task Force meeting, the idea of removing the overnight parking ban was floated as a way to address a racial and economic equity issue in town. I thought about the issue for several days, and collected my thoughts into an email which I sent to a few of the attendees on October 22. I&amp;rsquo;m sharing the body of that email so you can get a sense of my thinking on this issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thinking out loud about the BPS equity audit</title>
      <link>/thinking-out-loud-about-the-bps-equity-audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/thinking-out-loud-about-the-bps-equity-audit/</guid>
      <description>Context I&amp;rsquo;ve attended most of the school committee&amp;rsquo;s equity subcommittee meetings since February. On October 22, I sent an email to the equity subcommittee with some concerns that what had been described early in the process was not obviously what we were seeing in the implementation. I also wanted to share some goal thoughts for discussion, because that had been a topic at the October 19 meeting and few concrete goal ideas had been shared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Withdrawing my amendment to Article 10</title>
      <link>/withdrawing-article-10-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/withdrawing-article-10-amendment/</guid>
      <description>I first state my reasons for why I believe it makes sense to replace Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day. I then provide a number of different thoughts related to withdrawing my amendment.
The case for replacing Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day First, I don&amp;rsquo;t believe Columbus is deserving of a holiday or great respect. Like so many historic figures, his legacy is a mixed one, but it&amp;rsquo;s a mixed legacy that strikes me as far more negative than positive, as others have well articulated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My amendment for article 10</title>
      <link>/article-10-amendment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/article-10-amendment/</guid>
      <description>Summary of this post and my position on article 10 I support Article 10, the resolution to replace Columbus Day with Indigenous Peoples Day in Belmont, and I proposed an amendment to standardize the punctuation of the name of the day, to reduce the chance of misreading a particular sentence, and to address concerns about the inaccuracy of some historical claims.
I intend to vote in favor of Article 10 regardless of whether my amendment passes, though I believe my amendment includes some improvements and helps promote an important norm of intellectual honesty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preliminary analysis of FY20/FY21 assessment data</title>
      <link>/preliminary-assessment-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/preliminary-assessment-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Key takeaways  Many of us have wondered if assessments are increasing for everyone. About 26% of residential properties saw decreases in their assessed values between FY2020 and FY2021. (I&amp;rsquo;m defining residential properties as single families, condos, 2 and 3 families.) Many of us have also wondered about how assessments have changed for local apartment buildings. Some of them saw big decreases between FY2020 and FY2021. Finally, many of us have wondered about assessment changes for the local country club.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raising revenue and saving: The golf course and town pension fund</title>
      <link>/raising-revenue-and-saving-golf-course-and-saving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/raising-revenue-and-saving-golf-course-and-saving/</guid>
      <description>Raising revenue: The golf course The Belmont Country Club pays 25% of the tax rate for most of their land (the golf course). This is due to MA general law 61B.
Watch this presentation of the Board of Assessorsto the Warrant Committee (starting at 42:43) on March 3, 2021 for some discussion of this.
This issue has been around since the late 1970s.
The Structural Change Impact Group has had lobbying the state to change this law added to their list of ideas they will evaluate and potentially pursue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding property taxes and assessments</title>
      <link>/understanding-property-taxes-and-assessments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/understanding-property-taxes-and-assessments/</guid>
      <description>If, like me, you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been frustrated or confused by Belmont&amp;rsquo;s assessments or property taxes (e.g., why do they go up in Q3?) , I highly recommend watching this presesentation by the Board of Assessors to the Warrant Committee and the associated Q&amp;amp;A. It starts just before the two minute mark. I found it to be incredibly helpful and I learned a lot, especially from the Q&amp;amp;A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future plans for this site</title>
      <link>/future-plans-for-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/future-plans-for-this-site/</guid>
      <description>The plans  Whether I&amp;rsquo;m elected or not, I plan to release on this site an application that makes it easier to compare the voting records of our town meeting members. This is in the works. The town makes data available publicly, but the data is not consistent and there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of clean up to do before one can work with it. I also plan to share write-ups of information I&amp;rsquo;ve collected and my associated thoughts on issues related to the town (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me and why I&#39;m running</title>
      <link>/about-me-and-why-im-running/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-me-and-why-im-running/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m running for Town Meeting to represent Precinct 3 About me I’ve lived in Belmont for two years with my wife and now with our young daughter. I’m COO at MaxMind, a tech company headquartered in Waltham. My family and I very much enjoy the town, its parks, stores, the library, access to public transit, and the people we’ve met.
Why I&amp;rsquo;m seeking nomination I want to hold the town accountable for how it spends our tax money, and I want to ensure the services we receive in return run well and make sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>/page/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/page/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Last Updated: 2020-03-18 By visiting and using this website, you agree that your use of it is governed by this privacy policy.
This site makes use of Google Analytics to track and analyze visitor activity on the site (e.g., visits, popularity of different pages). This means that this website and Google have access to and may use your usage data. To learn about Google&amp;rsquo;s data practices, please read Google&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
